Oh, hello.  wait a minute.
Hello, Hee-mi, Baguhyeong, and Jeondol.  Nice to meet you.
Oh, I'm a little late because I was a little late in organizing things today
.
Nice to meet you too, Chin Eun-dong.
Hello, Chaihong.
Oh, news.
Uh, until the other broadcasters come in, I'll
tell you the good news a little later and then slowly tell you the
bad news first. No,
this
applies to you all too. It applies to some people,
but it
doesn't apply to everyone.  Well,
that's just a given.  Okay,
wait a minute.  The camera keeps making noise right now, so
I'll turn it back on.
Can it connect right away?  This has
probably been turned back on now.
Here and there.  Oh, so I
think this is the amount of contact I had.  Anything that
has accumulated dust or something.  The camera
USB and the main body USB are constantly making
contact, so it seems to be disconnecting intermittently.
When it disconnects, I will just briefly
turn it back on like this.   ah
.
Hello, Mr. Orun, Mr. Gong Jin-seon, and Mr. Kim So-hoon.  Nice to meet you, Nayeonna, Owl, and
Youngjin.   It's
so hard to get used to it.  I
've been trying for a month and I keep failing.
I'm so curious about what raw milk tastes like.
Oh, this is actually raw milk, so
the taste
isn't that different or anything.   It
tastes different because it's raw milk.
nice.  So the texture may be slightly different
.  This is
probably because it is not homogenized.
Well, even if it has that kind of fat content, it's
not homogeneous, so the
fat film itself is a bit bigger and
there are parts that feel a bit creamier in the mouth, but other than that, there's
really no problem other than the sterilization school
.
In fact, things like food and the breeding environment have a greater influence on taste
yes.  So in that sense, now the
taste is a little
different for each farm, and especially now that we
raise cattle in a cyclical manner, the feed is all
somewhat standardized, and most
farms feed similar things in expensive environments,
unlike milk farms, where we raise cattle on a small scale and pasture, the
taste is different for each farm, and
there are such parts.  yes.  I think the difference between farms
can be seen as a bit bigger
.  Especially for people
like me who have such a small number of cows and
it's a single farm milk, the
milk keeps going like this.
Why is this happening?
wait a minute.  I'll try again.
Ha, this is a camera. I don't know
if it would be better if I shot air with an air gun
.
Something
like that.  Anyway, the
taste of milk changes a lot depending on the season
.
Well, in the summer, it's really
hot.  And Holstein breed
cows are particularly sensitive to heat,
so their milk fat
content and milk solids content generally
drop.  Well, the protein content is also a bit
low.  Conversely, in winter, the
fat content increases further.  And
now, in spring and summer, we
especially eat a lot of green grass, so
there is a lot of damage due to that, and in winter, the fat
content is high, but
since we usually eat hay, the taste
changes accordingly and
there are many things.  This doesn't mean that eating grass
necessarily makes it taste better, or that
doing something necessarily makes it taste better
.
The taste is different depending on what kind of grass you eat, and to
some extent it may be a matter of taste,
but on the other hand, it's
like that dog, no, Japan,
what is it?
I can't remember English.  If you
go to Japanese restaurants,
there are quite a few cases where they serve food that lets you feel the season.
What, these days in the fall, especially in the fall, there are courses that
focus on using mushrooms,
and things like that
.
Being able to feel the seasons in that way can be an advantage for some people,
but for others, it's not so much a standardized
taste, but for those who want to
have a similar taste all the time, it
can be a bonus point.
Hello, Genie.
Ah, anyway
, ah, this is, these days, no, this year, there are a lot of things that are not
so cheap when it comes to raising milk
.
This time too, oh, this was really a big
mistake on my part, but
actually, I don't think
this has happened once this year,
and it almost never happened last year either, but I
made it rain.  As you
can see here, I used to
cover the tea bag with saporin like this and I
always cover it even when it rains
.  So, I forgot to cover it all this time, but
luckily it didn't rain and there was almost
no time when something would fall over, and
I just always covered it well, but oh, of
all days,
I
forgot this the night before yesterday.   I
forgot to cover this, but
it rained the day before yesterday, and it rained
quite heavily, and now it's
soaked through and
won't work.
Oh, so the kickboard broke
down, so I went to try to fix it the morning before yesterday, but it wouldn't turn on,
so I tried everything I could on my own, but it
just wouldn't work, so I called and called the farm machinery
repair center, and
this and that, but it
took a long time for it to be fixed.  So, in the end, I
ended up taking it to a repair center and they
replaced something called a havrator.
Ah, but anyway, I couldn't just wait for that at that time
because
it was a day when I had to dig up land and go to the castle in the middle of nowhere.
That's why, on that day, I
went out really early in the morning, earlier than usual.   I have to
finish that as early as possible, come home,
clean up the milk, and then go out and
work.  So now I have to go to Goseong,
so I have to go look at the land, so I
left early, but I couldn't even do anything
and just stamped my feet,
running here and there, trying to fix it but it didn't work out, so I
called the repair people who come out to fix it, but it didn't work out either, so I
ended up leaving it there and since
nothing else worked out, I just gave the kids food and said, "
Oh, there's nothing I can do."  I
didn't plan this, I just went and came back
thinking that I would finish the work in the evening, so I
went to dig the land and came back.  But
this is Gosung
, but really, it wasn't easy to
go to Gosung, Gangwon-do for a day trip to do some work
.  That
one way trip took 5 hours.
So, I drove for 5 hours to
meet the owner of the land and we
looked around here and there for about an hour
.
And now, I think it
was about an hour later
.  And now I'm back in the car again
.
Oh, driving, oh, so it's a
round trip of 10 hours.
I'm here
doing this, so just driving back and forth takes an hour a day,
so I go back and forth
twice, so
it's a round trip of 30 minutes once.  I drove for 11 hours that day,
but now it broke down anyway, so
I found this in the evening and luckily it's
fixed now. This fix, well,
until this morning, the
repairman said he tried everything, but it
didn't work.  The machine is
struggling.  Well, I thought, this
isn't working, that isn't working,
what should I do if this doesn't get fixed? I was
anxious and did
whatever I could, but luckily, I
heard in the afternoon that it was fixed, so I went home,
picked it up, and
had dinner.  The evening complex
went smoothly without any major issues, but
it was too late and I think
it was around 9:30 or 10:00
.  I
couldn't even squeeze it in the morning because it was so
late at night.  So,
the kids, the number of cars on the bridge was reduced significantly, and
the next morning it was really destroyed, and
since it's been quite some time since these kids gave birth to that kid,
and they're not kids that come out a lot these days
.
In that situation, I passed the pick without even thinking about it,
so it was a bit of a blow
.
Oh, so I
'm a little worried that the next generation will drop again.  I was thinking about increasing the fuel consumption
a little bit every day, but the
weather has gotten cooler recently, so it's been
slowly increasing, but if something like this
happens, it just drops right away and it
takes a long time to increase again
.  So, this is
actually something that I'm going to increase my mileage a bit next year or so,
and I've always
wanted to diversify my livestock.  It
's not just that I do that, I also want to raise chickens and
do this and that, but if I
raise a dairy cow and
other animals and do all that by myself, it's a lot of work, so I thought, what if I milk the cow only once a day and use the remaining time, which would have been spent milking it twice, to raise other animals
?  But if you
squeeze it twice and then squeeze it once, it's
not designed well,
so the milk kick and impact and things like that
can be quite big.  I felt something like that
a little bit on my skin.
Anyway, it was kind of like that.  It
would seem like it would be much easier if they slept once a day from the time they first hatched, but
in fact, this was not good news.
So, I think that the milk supply has decreased so much that it will be
difficult to purchase the vertical rights, even though it has been like that for a while now
.
Hello, Gangsub Gwanjeodong.
Nice to meet you.
Anyway, if this
was bad news, the good news is
that I saw the land.
It rained quite a bit at this time and
what
and what, but I don't know for sure.   It's
not like I have a lot of experience going around to different fields.
When it rains or something.
I don't know if this is how it is for everyone,
but it
seems like the water is accumulating here too.
That thing I'm using right now,
if it rains a lot, it
gets really sticky.
Anyway, most of the land you see in the picture is
like that.  Oh, there's a little more here,
but anyway, the land here is in the middle of
Gosung, but really, if you go from Gimcheon to Gosung, I
originally had the mindset that I would go anywhere as long as there was land,
but I really feel like I'm running around like a grasshopper,
going from Taebaek to
Gimcheon and back to Gosung
.  But, but I'm having a
good conversation with the person who lives here, so I
think I might end up going here.
I've
prepared a bit more and I
'm going to ask you again to let me borrow it in this way and that way.  Actually, I spoke to you on
the phone today and spoke to you again, but
after watching the video of Doctor 3,
there are a few videos of me being interviewed there.  That's how you
got to know me and now
you leave comments on my videos.
Come see the land once.  So I
went there after receiving that call. Yes.  Well, I
was thinking that there was no rule that said it couldn't be done in any way, and I felt really lost about doing anything else.
yes.  yes.  Anyway, on my recent visit, I
realized that even if I were to
borrow the land from this person and not be able to do it, I
was able to hear a lot of great insights in a short amount of time.
So there were a lot of moments where it felt like something really new was
opening up,
but
if you look at it over a long period of time, it's
unfortunate that this place is now just a regular
place.
So, this is actually,
ah, well, it's not unconditional,
but anyway, if you want to
raise animals a little more freely and not be tied down by things like treatment facilities and
strange things that are useless from my perspective,
investing capital,
time, and things like that, and
having to manage them, then it's
really good if the land is grassland according to the Grassland Act.
So, it is pasture land and is considered pasture under the Pasture Land Act
.  This is just a
field with grass planted on it, but it's not called a pasture. There's
something called the Pasture Land Act in our country, and
there's a definition of a pasture in that Pasture Land Act.  So,
if the pasture land is like this, it
is good because it is designated by law for livestock grazing, but
right now, it is not a pasture
.  But I also thought that even if not right now,
later on,
if I create a pasture or if
this person has one or creates a new pasture in the future, I
might go there and do it again
.  So,
Dam-bi and Majora, nice to meet you.
yes.  Anyway, the
people who are looking for land are no longer
worried, so although it is
a bit frustrating that the cows are not producing milk,
they are feeling a bit
better.
Of course, there is still a lot of work to be done
.
Just looking at the stuff I have right now,
it's quite a lot. There
are things like saws,
circular saws,
angle grinders, bowls, etc., and
strange drills and all kinds of
miscellaneous items. Just looking at the house alone, it's quite a lot. But I
'm storing all of that in a vinyl greenhouse that we're using as a warehouse. But since we
don't have that here yet, I have to
build one myself. If I build it in a misunderstanding, I'll
be able to bring the stuff I have now and store it.
Oh, so that's why I think I
need to move around a bit more quickly, but the problem is that it's
too much work to go back and forth while working here,
it's a 10-hour round trip.  So,
I think we need to think a little bit about how to proceed with this.   I'm
thinking that I should finish up in Gimcheon a few days early and then go. On the other hand, it'll
cost a lot of money to start over next year, and since
this year's crop failed and I have
n't been able to save much capital, I'm
also thinking that I should somehow save up a ton more by milking milk for one more day and selling milk certificates. I still do
n't know what to do.   I
guess I need to think about it seriously again and then proceed.
So next year, if we go here, we will
probably be able to increase the number of cows a bit more
.
Um, actually, I want to raise chickens properly, but
actually, there's more than just this one plot of land
.  There's
another piece of land right below here that's much larger, maybe
twice as big
.
Oh, but this is actually,
if I were to rent a large field, there would be a limit to the number of animals I could raise on that field
unless I installed a milk powder processing facility, and
things like that.
Also, the landowner is worried about whether I can properly make a profit by renting a large piece of land and paying the expensive rent. So, for
now, I think I'll just rent this one
.  Anyway, I
was thinking that if things get easier in the future, it would be good to raise chickens, meat chickens, and maybe even laying hens.   I
always think about how I want to increase the thickness to a certain extent.
hmm.  Bringing in the chicks, that is,
bringing in the chicks, and then
finding a place to slaughter them.
If these two things could be resolved, it would
be really worth it. What's great about Gosung is that unlike other places, they basically say that you can't raise pigs or chickens, but in
Gosung, I've
been keeping an eye on Gosung for a long time. There are places
like Pyeongchang where the distance restrictions for housework are
very short, but in
my opinion, Boseong has
very reasonable regulations.
Let's see, it's not just the youngest.
This is an ordinance regarding restrictions on livestock farming in Goseong County
.  But
if you look here, they are designating a restricted area for over-production, and
now this is a restricted area
.  But what's really good about this is that you
can't raise it in any restricted area
.  But actually,
since these places are usually not that big, the
biggest problem is how far the
distance between buildings is restricted in some restricted areas
.  But these are
usually
chickens, ducks, pigs, etc., and they
are over 700 to 1000 meters.
And
if there are more than a few, it all applies.
So, as you can see here, a
restricted area has been designated, but the following exceptions have been
made.  And the
exception is that the number of animals that can be raised is 20 or less, including pets and livestock
that are not for
profit
.
There are also places where there are usually ten other kids.  So, for
these types of rapids, you
shouldn't raise fewer than a few, but
if you want to raise two or 30,
in principle, they
should all be kept at least 1,000m apart.  It's
almost the same in every other local government.
Almost Goseong.
I think there used to be one or two or three more, but
now it seems like there is only Goseong.
I've searched almost all of these places
.  I looked up all the
local government ordinances across the country regarding restrictions on family ministry,
and I organized them all.
But when I looked this time,
there wasn't a single one like this except for Goseong.
Only Gosung is
now somewhat re-established, isn't that right? This
doesn't make sense.  A
person raising one dog is subject
to the same distance restrictions as a person raising 200,000 dogs
.  But Gosung is not that kind of
ignorant method,
it is a range of allowances based on distance, so the breeding
range is set like this.
In the case of a large fish, if you raise less than 30,000, you only need to
keep it 250m away.
And even in the case of pigs, if you
raise less than 1,000, you only need to be 500 meters away
.
If you want to raise more than 3,000, you need to be more than 1,000 here, but
if you have less than 1,000, you can be close, and
if you have less than 100, you
can just 200 meters away from the milk sword, so
it's really great.  So, for
those of you who want to raise livestock on a small scale like me, do
n't
say, "Here, let's say we have 1,000 pigs."  No,
how do you raise a thousand pigs?
People like me who want to graze.  Of course,
pigs can't graze, but they still
go.  The
basic requirement is 30,000 chickens.  30 thousand.  So,
if it's a place where it doesn't have to be that far apart, like 250m to 450m, then what can I do?   It's
not like it's 3,000 or something like that,
30,000 is the basic unit.
So what I'm saying is, in reality, this
is only true unless there are more than 5 chickens or something like that.  If complaints had been pouring in here, the
law would have been changed a long time ago.  But
I don't know if it's because profitability has dropped to this point that no one is building livestock farms, but
anyway, since
there are no major problems, I think this is continuing
.  So, this
is a reasonable way to set regulations based on scale, but
other things are just blindly done with the sole intention of unconditionally banning livestock farming, and they are just saying that
you absolutely should not do it if it is over 1000m
.  Don't do it, that's what regulation is.
So, considering these circumstances and those
circumstances, we have a lot of regulations that are not made to
be like this, but rather to say, “Don’t do it unconditionally.”
Most areas are like that.  But it's
really nice that it's like this here
.  I had that thought.
yes.  In that sense, yes, you can raise chickens
nearby, as long as they don't reach 30,000
.  I also wanted to raise poultry like ducks and quails,
so I
was able to do that.
Hello, Kwon In-ah.   I
sometimes eat Cheon-Gyeol-Gyeot, but when I
bought plain yoghurt and ate it, I
got hives.  The
problem must be Yoo Seong-gyun.
hmm.  That could be the case.
hmm.  yes.  That might be possible
.  Well, to be exact, I don't
really know.   I
think we can say that we have almost secured the land.
Oh, I
guess I should tell those people who contacted me here and there to find land that I found it.
hmm.
Oh, but as I said earlier,
this isn't a grassland, and unfortunately,
I'm just saying that I'm full,
but it's not quite right to say that I'm disappointed
.  Before that, I
couldn't even think about renting grassland.  But
that's why I'm talking about the grassland
.  There, the
land is designated as grassland according to the Grassland Act, and
this is written in the regional district designation
.  So I saw this and was
really excited thinking, "Oh, this is grassland," but
it turned out to be a mistake and it was
actually grassland.
But now,
if you don't want to build a Jackson Moonyu processing facility, you have
to do it on this scale.
In the case of livestock sheds, the
area should be less than 100 square meters for small cattle,
less than 200m2 for chickens or ducks, and
in grazing facilities, the number of small horses
should be less than nine, and the number of ducks should
be less than 1,000. But since
this is a small cattle shed, you can't raise eight dairy cows and
1,000 ducks
like that. You have to do it
proportionally so that the total sum
doesn't add up to 1.
So, you can raise up to eight cows, but if
you raise four, you have
50% left, so we
can raise exactly 750 cows, and so
on.
hmm.  yes.  Anyway,
I think that's why it feels like it's happening inside this
.
yes.  But where is this place?
hmm.   If I
had gone somewhere else, I would
n't have been able to raise Dai at all, but if I
had a little more confidence that I would be able to continue raising Dai in the long run without worry once the trial risk is resolved, I
think it would be really, really good for me to raise Dai too.  That's why I want to avoid building powdered milk processing
facilities and do everything else, but
in the case of a small business like that, a
new law was recently established, so
I think it's not listed here because it has
n't been updated yet,
but it's something like
this.
How much should be given per cow for the livestock service facility area?
There is something like this.  But this
is a new facility that was built this time, so it is much
smaller.  Because the Jersey is now
smaller than the average Holstein.
So, based on the standard of 50M, which is used to
determine whether a livestock industry permit or registration is required, up
to eight animals are allowed as long as they do not meet the 50M standard.
Then, since the net farm facility is no longer required to
be deleted, it corresponds to eight animals, and the
livestock area is less than 50m2, so it
can be resolved by simply registering it as a family business.
So, what this
means is that, if you
raise them, you can increase the maximum mileage without being subject to any strange and difficult legal regulations.
Of course, if you
think about it as a problem, like a calf or something like that, that's
not all.
In the end, if we want to do something more serious, we'll
have to figure out whether to build a processing facility or go to pasture, but anyway, based on what
I'm doing at the level I'm at right now, I think it
would be great to raise Jerseys.
Even if Holsteins
produce more milk than Jerseys, if the
mileage is that different,
Jerseys will produce more milk,
and the quality is also much higher,
as well as the fat content, high-fat content, and milk
protein.
yes.  But the price of bringing it in would be
very expensive, it wouldn't be easy to obtain,
and if it were to be closed down and disposed of later in court, the
loss would be even greater, etc.,
so I'm still a little hesitant
.
Oh, but what's really interesting is that
you're going to Goseong.
So, they say there isn't a single dairy farm in Gosung
.  If I go in
and raise the sect, I will
become the only sect leader in Gosung
.
So, I found this a bit strange.
No, I
have this feeling that there's nothing I can do to raise it. Um,
if there's a problem with the thyroid, is it
bad for the nose?
Oh,
no.  It has
nothing to do with the thyroid.
And I'm not sure what problem you're talking about,
but anyway,
whether it's hyperthyroidism or hypothyroidism, I do
n't think there's any connection between cheese and that to my knowledge.
Hello, Mr. K.  Nice to meet you.
I think the name of the Japanese Jersey pudding was Sopapjeong.  yes.  The breed that we usually know as Jersey
is Holstein.
yes.  You know, the spotted cows we're all familiar with
?  These
are the Holstein breed of cattle,
and there is also a Jersey breed that looks like this
.
There are also some that stand together at the same time.   The
kids are a little smaller now and they produce a little less milk,
yes.  However, the solids content is still
much higher.  It has a much higher fat content and a
much higher protein content.
And above all, it endures summer better
.  Actually, I think this is a very
important issue for me.  So,
even if Holsteins produce more milk than Jersey cows,
that is
based on the Holsteins eating and living well just like Jersey cows on a regular basis.
Holsteins are very vulnerable to heat and
humidity
.
Oh, so in the summer, when the sun is
shining and it's really hot and humid, if you let them out to
pasture and go outside, I do
n't think they can handle it very well
.  The impact was really big, and while I
was working here for three years, every
summer, the cows' fuel consumption
really hit rock bottom and they had a really
hard time.
This
is like a normal farm, the floor is a [ __ ] field anyway,
but if you dig up [ __ ], it's a celebration.   They
urinate and poop there all the time,
and there's a fan on top that
sprays water and
keeps spinning, so it heats them up,
and I think the cows don't
suffer as much from the heat.
In conventional livestock farming.  But I'm out in the pasture,
so I
can't turn on a fan, and
the ground might be
a little damp when there's a morning drizzle, but it's
not damp.
So I think they'll get more sunburned if they graze any longer.
I made a sidewalk to
provide some shade, but honestly, the shade is
n't that big.
Because of things like that, I
think summer is a bit harsher for me, and for the cows, if we just
consider the heat.  In that respect,
rather than raising a Bolstein and having it cut in half to withstand the summer heat, I
think it would be better to
bring in a Jersey breed that can withstand the heat better, I
don't know how well the Jersey
breed will do, but I don't
know for sure since I haven't tried it, so I do
n't think they'll be able to withstand that level of heat anyway.
Hello, Eun-kyung Kim.
What causes dementia?
The disease we call dementia itself
is not just one thing, and
Alchamer
cannot say unconditionally that this is the cause with just one reason
.
hmm.
But even though it
's been quite some time since then,
should we say it's still fresh?  Well, relatively
recently, one of the things that people have been discussing
a lot and pointing out as a cause
is insulin resistance.
yes.  This is because plaque builds up and
so on, and so on, and so forth. So, while we
sleep, our brains
constantly wash themselves to
prevent plaque buildup, and
there are parts that do that, but now that's not working very well, and
a lot of plaque builds
up, and this leads to Alchamo, and so on.
This has been the mainstream for a while
.  Brain plaque buildup
.  So dementia treatments have
always focused on removing those plaques
.
But actually, this was a huge scandal a few years ago.
The dementia drugs that had been approved by the FDA and were being sold in large quantities and making a lot of money were actually ineffective, and the fact that the
FDA knew that they were ineffective led to the
revelation that they were ineffective, and now it has
become a huge scandal.
There was a huge controversy.  yes.  Well, actually, I
can just ignore those things since I already made all the money
.
In that way, they
sell it as an effective treatment for dementia, but
in reality, it has no effect and it
is a disease that is now extremely difficult to treat.
Well, this is the only story that is told, but
in the mainstream medical world.  But
then again, on the other hand,
this is not really a medicine,
but anyway, I don't know
why it is not accepted in mainstream medicine, or why
it is not pointed out as a major cause, but
anyway,
one of the causes that is pointed out a lot is insulin resistance in the brain.
DeMarin Jackson says that insulin resistance is when the
body produces a lot of insulin, but
the tissues become insensitive to insulin and
do not properly accept the insulin and draw blood sugar and other nutrients into the cells through the action of insulin receptors.  That is the most representative
mechanism.  This is a typical symptom.
As a result of the insulin accuracy, blood sugar levels are high.  The brain now
uses pods as its main energy source.  If ketone bodies
don't come out, especially, and
even in the ketosis state where ketone bodies come out,
30% of the energy must
be obtained from pods, so pods are
very important. In the brain,
blood sugar is high and pods are
overflowing, but the brain's insulin sensitivity is too
strong and it
can't accept the glucose
.  To use energy sources.
So, there is an abundance of food and energy sources,
but people are starving to death
.
yes.
So, if you actually calculate insulin resistance, the
symptoms of dementia can improve a lot,
or if you
just give topical ketone supplements to dementia patients,
even if their insulin sensitivity is the same and their blood sugar level is not controlled at all, just that alone can
immediately produce some cognitive effects
.   The
type of chiton is literally just
eating the chiton itself with your mouth.
Ketones are ketone bodies that are naturally produced in the body when the
glucagon is depleted because we do not eat carbohydrates and the
glucagon is depleted, but
now that the
blood sugar is high and glucagon is not
produced, you
can still take them as supplements
.  But if you eat it like that,
or whatever, there is that too.  If you
eat things like coconut oil or something like that,
they are immediately converted into ketone bodies
.  There are things like that, but anyway,
if you eat something like external ketones like this, the ketone bodies go up and the blood ketone
concentration goes up, and
even if I have insulin resistance, I can use the ketone bodies, so
yes, there are cases where the cognitive effect is shown almost immediately by using the ketone bodies
.   I
guess you're wondering what's most important for blood growth?  I think you're wondering what's most important for blood growth,
and this is the same thing: there's just one
thing that's most important.
Well, you just need to take care of this one thing.
Of course, you're not looking for just one thing and
trying to do just that, but
I think it's difficult to pick out the most important thing or something like that.
Well, first of all,
not everything can be quantified.
What's important about growing taller? For example,
proper sleep, which can be influenced by
various growth hormones and
other things,
sufficient protein intake, sufficient
mineral intake, and
sufficient fat-soluble vitamins so that the minerals can function well,
and other
things like preventing metabolic diseases and insulin resistance, such as
not eating a lot of carbohydrates or not eating as much as you can eat,
and proper exercise, going
out and getting some sunlight,
there are probably many things, but since
we can't put a number on how much each of these contributes,
I think it's very appropriate to try to figure out what's most important,
and above all, I
think it's meaningless.  Knowing that, the
most important thing is, for example, if you
look at the ratio among these, for example, there is
something with an importance of 8%, some with
9%, some with 8.5%, some with 5%, some with
7%, but there is one thing
with 11%, so it took first place.  So the
most important thing is, let's say, fat-soluble vitamin intake, which accounts for that 11%
.
So, if you only focus on taking fat-soluble vitamins, you'll only be
able to get 11% of the recommended daily intake, even if you try hard to get the most important ones
.  Then there is no reason to discuss it
.  Anyway, you probably
want to grow as tall as possible,
so I don't think there's any point in arguing about what's most important.
In the
end, it's all about living a healthy life. It
helps with growing taller, it
helps with not getting sick, it
helps with not getting arthritis, it
helps with not getting diabetes, and in the end, it's
all similar.   I
have hypothyroidism and was told to limit dairy products
.  If I say something like that,
I think it would be a good idea to get into the habit of asking back why I'm asking you to put restrictions in place.
So,
maybe there is some scientific basis for this that I don't
know about
.
So, if you listen to that and tell me what you think,
I
can learn from it, and if we
look into it together, I
might have something to say.
But if you
just say, “Someone said that,” then, as far as
I know, what I can hear right now has
nothing to do with it.
This is all there is.
Milk also contains some iodine, is that
why?  Oh, that's
nonsense.  And
I don't think anyone would be harmed by the iodine in milk.  Rather, if you
don't eat seafood, you
should look for foods that are naturally concentrated in yogurt, such as milk.
Hello, Aprince.   It
may be difficult for a modern woman to completely cut out processed foods or edible oils while pregnant, but I try to provide as many top-quality
vitamins as possible.
I don't think there's anything more important than quitting eating fatty foods, but
the point of the question is,
in addition to the video you uploaded, would it
be helpful to buy and read Celly's book?  I
'm going to watch that video over and over again, but will it
be more helpful if I read the book as well?  Oh,
books, of course. So, each person
has their own preferred source of information, depending on where and how they receive information. So, even if I explain the same
information
in a video,
some people may naturally prefer to read a book
.  So,
depending on that aspect, reading books
can be incredibly helpful, and
above all, they don't always provide the same information
.  So, since the book covers much more in-
depth content, the match
itself is better.
That's why, among the books by Selly Palo,
there is a separate book for child care, that is, for the six families.  And
since the book will be filled with content related to the six families,
it will likely
be about pregnancy, childbirth, and such.  So,
I think you'll be able to see a lot more content by reading books like that.
But since it's an original text, you need to be able to speak English
.
hmm.
But actually, of course, it's
better to do it anytime than not to do it, so even
when you get older and
become a grandmother or grandfather, if your health is deteriorating,
it's good to watch your diet, but
it's always a shame that you
start paying attention to your diet after you get pregnant,
so this is actually like that, for
example, I lived until I was in my 80s
.  I just lived like that,
eating whatever I liked, both good and bad, and
now that I'm in my 80s, my health is not
good.  But then,
if I had eaten healthily for the past 80 years, it would have been meaningless after this
.  It's not that it
doesn't have any meaning, but rather that
it doesn't really
feel that important.
Now, I
wonder what's the use of lamenting the passage of time in the 80s?   I
just have to work hard at what I can do now
.  Oh, but I
got pregnant only a
few months ago, so I can't help but think about
how much better it would have been if I had paid a little more attention a year or two ago, even before I got pregnant. I
always feel a little regretful about that
.  They say that when you fix a crab,
a lot of things are already decided.
How much of this vitamin A warehouse in the mother's body is filled with,
how much of this topographic vitamin
is filled with, and when the cells in the baby's body
differentiate, the first
thing that is created is the heart, and if
there is a lack of vitamin A at that time and differentiation
does not occur properly, the
probability of being born with a heart problem increases greatly.
What if we had paid attention to this a little earlier?
So many modern people, so many
people, when they get pregnant, they
take prenatal vitamins and are more careful about what they eat.
Of course,
there are people who take advantage of that and eat more junk food, but they
just say they want to eat the baby,
or that that's the only food they're craving right now,
or they
can't eat other foods, or they have morning sickness or something
.  There are cases like that, but
overall, I think it's a good thing to be a little more
careful and mindful about what you eat
.  Oh,
but now I think it's still a bit of a shame that I just
lived my life however I wanted and then started worrying about it after I got pregnant
.  Of course, there are some couples who plan to get
pregnant and live a healthy life without any plans, but
usually, most of them are
older couples who have trouble conceiving and getting pregnant.
Younger couples just do whatever they can and when they do get pregnant, they
say, "Oh, I got pregnant."  But
in fact, it's already been over a month since I found out I was pregnant,
and
if I say now, "Okay, let's
do something about it,"
it's actually quite late
.  That's what it was like in the
80s, and I wish we had done better 80 years ago.
Of course, just because we
talked a little more about it a few months ago, two months ago, three months ago, it
may not have affected the trend or anything like that,
but anyway, I wish we had paid a little more attention even six months ago, a year ago.
That's what I regret.
But anyway, what happened is what happened, and what
happened is what happened, and we can't go back in time, so
we have to do what we can now.
Hello, Jayoung.
Is this the new Kangwon National University?
yes.  I think I'll probably go to Goseong
.  To Gosung, Gangwon-do.   I
was currently in Gimcheon, which is located in Gyeongnam, and then
I
went to Goseong, which is close to North Korea, on the Palseon River.
Nice to meet you, Gyu.  Have
you ever seen a case where hair loss improved with Carnivore
?  There are so many people who have improved their eyesight
.  Just visit our cafe.
Hello Universe.  Since protein
is absorbed into the body in the form of amino acids anyway,
there is talk that even if we take collagen, it doesn't have the desired effect, such as improving skin.
What do you think?
Those
are just stories that are told with a very simple understanding.  Our body does not necessarily
absorb it only in the form of amino acids
.
There are clearly parts that are absorbed as peptides, and so
there are quite a few parts where physiological peptides come in that state and play a role, and
above all, in the case of collagen, you
can think of it as marking collagen with a synthesizing element and painting the collagen peptide with the color of the collagen peptide.  Now we
can check wherever we go.  So, if you
color the collagen peptide and then
eat it, it will all be broken down into amino acids
and absorbed, and then it will just
disappear and be over. But we have already confirmed that it goes to the skin, joints, or other places where collagen should go
in the form of a complete collagen peptide
.  There are papers that have confirmed this through research
.   When
you eat that collagen, the collagen goes to the collagen tissue
.
That's why it's now a bit ignorant to just say things like, "It's useless because it's already
been broken down into cryptographic pieces anyway
."
And anyway, it's not meaningless because you can eat the amino acids needed to create collagen tissue
through collagen
.
What kind of laundry detergent do you use?
And what about using salt water when making pickles
?  Or I'm curious about using activated carbon or water,
etc.  I'm still using a cheap,
no-brand laundry detergent that I bought a long time ago
.  Well, I
did a lot of rowing.  But
among the soaps I use,
there is one that I use as Gangcheong.   The
soap here is
made of pure soap ingredients.
It's just soap.  Pure soap.
But here, I think it would be okay to just buy something with pure soap powder in it, without any
strange ingredients or anything like that
.   It's
cheap but very clean.  Ingredients.
And I think salt water gargling is good
.  I just
use a toothbrush without salt water
.  yes.  Salt water, so you
mix a lot of salt in it, then
soak your teeth in it, soak the toothbrush in it,
take it out, and then use it to brush your teeth.  This
seems like a bit of a national rule.  Yes,
with that salt
.   It
seems good.
Is it okay to take 10g of cold-extracted olive oil with an acidity of 0.1 in a single-use stick pack (111) for a long time while eating butter?  But
I think that the reason you eat this much is because you think it will be good for you.
So, I do
n't think we would eat olive oil that is packaged in a stick form for its flavor, and it
would feel like we are taking a nutritional supplement
. But there is no reason why we should eat olive oil like we are taking a nutritional supplement.
If I had to be specific, I'm not feeling very well
.
And that's that too, but
if you're just eating it for the taste, I
think that's okay, but this
comes in a 10g disposable stick, and the
disposable sticks are all
made of plastic.  There will be Miss Plastic in it, and it's
like you have to eat that Miss Plastic.
So, if you want to enjoy the taste of olive oil, it would be
better to just buy a delicious glass bottle of olive oil and drink it
.
Why don't you use toothpaste?
Toothpaste, like regular toothpaste, fluoride
toothpaste, etc., is
also there because you don't want to ingest fluoride on its own
.  And I
don't want to put all the chemicals in it in my mouth.  I don't
even want to rub the activator in my mouth
.  Well, I guess I'll
have to ingest a certain amount, but I
don't want to eat it.  And
above all, it is not necessary.
There's no reason to use toothpaste, so there's no reason to
spend money on something bad for your body and
put it in your body
.  That's why it's so
popular, so it's
like we really need something, and I think
a lot of the things we consume these days are
like that.
Oh, actually, things like detergent are like that too.
It's not like we use things like dishwashing detergent,
or anything like that. We don't really
have to wash the dishes so diligently
or always make them look squeaky clean,
but we act
like we have to and just
use detergent like that. We don't need
shampoo or
foam cleanser or anything like that when we wash our faces or shower or wash our hair. Of
all the animals living on Earth, we're the only ones who
use foam cleanser and wash our faces.
So, it doesn't make sense to
need that kind of thing to wash our bodies and keep them clean.
On top of that, I'm not sure if humans
even use home cleansing.
Has it been 50 years?   I do
n't think home cleansing has been around for 50 years, and
soap has been around for a long time before that, but I
don't think people would rub soap on their face and wash it off.
That skin feels really bad too
.
I think it's probably about the same as using shampoo,
so humans themselves don't use
them, and no other animals use them
either. But they're all unnecessary, and
people think they're so obvious that they're necessary, so
now we
buy and use everything. And
after that, since we've removed the oil from our faces, we have to
reapply oil, so we
put on some creamy stuff or something
.
That's true, so let's say that functional
cosmetics are used for certain needs, but
there are also products that are applied on a daily basis.   I
feel like I'm living a life full of useless things,
like applying skin toner and lotion without really thinking
about it, even though I don't need them
. I don't know if I should say I've been fooled by marketing, or if I've been brainwashed, or if I've fallen for consumerism.   This
may be a legitimate question, but I suspect I have erectile dysfunction,
would you recommend against Viagra?
But in the first place, Viagra is not
a treatment for erectile dysfunction, but rather it temporarily masks the symptoms
.  It
doesn't treat the cause.
So, doesn't it have exactly the same effect as taking a short dose of insulin when blood sugar is high
?
Well, just
like there are times when insulin is needed right away, if
patients with diabetes are eating something, that's
right, Mr. Imsul.  What should I do?
As with all medicines, there will always be moments when you need to use them, but
that
won't solve the cause, so I would like to recommend
thinking about ways to fix the cause and
putting them into practice
.  I cook frozen squid and
eat seven of them a day.   You should
eat oysters, and since there are a lot of insulin sensitivity
issues these days, if there is anything suspicious about it, you should be concerned, and you should also
get good sleep, and if
there are any other things that can lower testosterone, you
should control those things well.
Could consuming the genitals of a dream help?  It's
true that Gohan contains tesosterone and things like that.
Of course,
there are a lot of irons and things like that.  So, since
the nutrients that make up our body are contained within that body, we
can receive some help in that respect as well, and we
can consume some testosterone and
there are such aspects, but in
fact, in my opinion,
rather than trying to solve it by eating something specific,
I think there might be something else that is causing the problem in a bigger picture.
So,
rather than trying to improve a healthy diet by adding some ideas to it, I think it
would be more effective to eliminate the bad things
.
How does fluoride affect our bodies
?
hmm.
Actually, fluoride,
oh, come to think of it, in my recent
videos, there were people talking about fluoride, and
there were people who saw something strange somewhere and said really strange things, but I didn't reply because I was annoyed,
but anyway, in Korea, it's not like
that, but in foreign countries, especially in the
US, there are
quite a few things that add fluoride to tap water.  This is
because back in the old days, when there was a lot of leftover Bulagazine and hydrofluoric acid gas from war, they were wondering what to do with it, and they thought, "Oh, I can just burn it in water," and now it's almost like that.
But then why did you end up in the water anyway
?   When
we eat fluoride, it enters our bones and
provides resistance to cavity-
causing bacteria.
So, if you use fluoride, your teeth
will not rot easily.  It
builds up resistance to things like mittens bacteria.
That's why, for public health, it would be good to
mix fluoride in water and
have everyone drink it.
It was something like this.
yes.  So now, the iron
can be used to treat the environmentally polluting hydrofluoric acid gas that was difficult to deal with by mixing it with water
.
hmm.  hmm.  But I have
n't looked into it properly, but I know that there have been a lot of recent research results showing that the oral hygiene and anti-cavity effects
of fluoride, which were generally known,
were very difficult to achieve, and in fact, there were no significant effects on public health
.
On the other hand,
it is said that in addition to the so-called positive effects, there are also various negative effects.
hmm.   The
most important thing was the hippocampus, right?
It acts on a specific part of the brain,
reducing brain function and
lowering IQ, especially in growing children.  There are quite a few papers showing that when you are exposed to a lot of fluoride, your
IQ literally drops
.
Oh, there are probably a few more besides that,
but I think those are the most representative ones, and that's all
I know about them now
.
Is there anything better than goat milk or something like that?
Well,
for those who are allergic to cow's milk, dairy products
might be better.  There are people who
are allergic to sheep
but not cows,
so it's a bit of a reciprocal thing, but
for those people, goat meat might be better and
easier to digest
.  Goats
have smaller fat sacs, so
cows have larger fat sacs, so it may
feel a bit creamier in our mouths,
but this is
only when the fat is not homogeneous.  But
if you do this artificially, it is not good because it
is harmful in itself, but
anyway, if we talk about raw
beef that is not homogenous,
goats are
originally somewhat homogenous, so even
if you leave it alone, the
fat layer does not
rise to the level of cream.  Even when I think about it, only a little
comes to mind.
So, that might make it a little easier to digest
.
Well, Kazinnan's white matter,
Paulstein's white matter, and even the jerseys
are mostly mixed with A12, but unless they are from
a jersey that was selected for the 882 gene,
those kinds of things might be
better for some people
.
In terms of other effects, they are almost similar, but
goat milk has some nutrients that are a little less abundant than milk, and some that are
more abundant.
In the case of vitamins, the acidity
is usually lower.  So, there is a
severe deficiency of folic acid and such.
However,
when we take raw milk as the standard, such as lactoperoxidase,
rather than based on raw milk, the protective defense factors in raw milk that
strongly suppress certain bacteria,
such as protective factors,
protective factors, and such, the
protective factors in milk that protect the young,
lactoperoxidase is a representative example and
has much greater hunting power.
I think it might be because the wild cats are a bit dirtier or something.
Do you think psychological factors could be the cause?   It
could be a psychological cause.
Well, of course it is.  But, it does
n't have to be psychological, there
could be a problem with your lifestyle habits.  Eating
can be a problem, but it's not so much that you're lacking something,
but rather that you're eating something you shouldn't be eating
.  There could be something else that triggers insulin sensitivity, whether it's a
dietary or lifestyle
habit,
or it could be a stress issue.
Or it could just be some other psychological issue
.  Actually, it
may not be just one reason, it may be a combination of several reasons, or
something like that.
There is a 65-year-old woman who does not eat oil at all, but she had a lot of symptoms of anaemia, so I had her
take omega-3.
Are there any other good oil capsules? You
should take these capsules.
Can't I just eat eggs and meat
?  You eat butter, you
eat milk, you eat cheese,
but if you don't eat any oil at all,
how do you eat?
Do you make chicken breast with rice?
But
since you can take omega 3 in capsules, I
don't think you mean you have to intentionally avoid eating fat.
So, why don't you just eat eggs and cheese
?
Avoid oils due to childhood trauma.
So, when you eat oil, like pork belly
oil or
something else, like boiled eggs or unpasteurized cheese, you don't feel like you're
eating oily food or anything
like that
.
So,
is that a trauma that you shouldn't eat something because it has oil in it?  Or
what kind of
eggs do you eat?
I think it would be good for you to eat a lot of eggs.
Say no to cheese butter.   You
should eat a lot of eggs, you know.
But if you eat walnuts, you can consume a lot of arachidonic acid,
so
you eat a lot of walnuts but
can't eat fish?
Fish is also not really good for you as it is just an omega 3 capsule
.  So, you
must have been eating it in some way.  He's 65 years old. If he had
n't eaten any oil during that time,
he would have passed away already. He
must have been eating fish or something consistently in some way,
but it would be good if he increased the amount a little.
Well, it
might be difficult to eat a high-fat diet like a phytogenic diet right now,
so you should try to get as much essential fatty acids as possible,
fill up on foods rich in fat-soluble vitamins,
and get the rest of your energy
from carbohydrates.  I think that's how it should be
.  So, if you
eat as much egg yolk as possible,
eat as much seafood as possible,
eat a lot of liver, get some sunlight,
eat plenty of meat, and eat rice, I
think you'll be fine.
yes.
I think it would be good to give them a lot of eggs.
Well, if you can't eat fish, you
should at least take omega 3 capsules, but
yes.  If you eat a lot of eggs while taking omega 3 capsules,
eggs are
called brain food in English-speaking countries.
yes.  Eggs contain all the nutrients the brain needs
.
When I go cannibalistic, I get really thirsty
hmm.  well.
If you have just started drinking honey, your
kidneys may not be able to retain water well, and as water leaks out, the
electrolyte balance may be disrupted,
which may cause you to feel a bit thirsty.   You
might have eaten too much salt, or you
might have cooked the meat too dry
.   I'm not
sure if you get really thirsty after doing Carnivore.  I don't think that's likely
.
Well, if you compare it to someone who just eats salad as a treat,
I think it might make you a little thirstier.  Those
people are now eating a ton of those vegetables, literally kilometers at a time, and they're
consuming
a lot of water from that.   When I
try to tell people around me about the restaurant, they do
n't want to hear it and find it annoying.  I'm
going to live by eating the same way I used to.
That's usually the case.   I'm
thinking of eating some frozen chicken breast because it's cheap, but I'm worried it
won't be very filling.
Well, it's a bit lower than the original,
but it's still a good song
.
Well, but actually,
if you compare it to cheap beef and pork,
they are both equally cheap.  Well, if you compare it to buying it in bulk from places like Meat Box, it
's not that cheap.
Takaseumsal.  Yeah, I guess I'm
wondering if it's really necessary to go that far just because of the price
.
It's okay not to eat vegetables at all.   There does
n't seem to be any reason why you should eat vegetables.
By any chance, what brand of butter do you use?  I
eat anchor butter.
How do I detox from the coronavirus vaccine?
hmm.  well.
Well,
as for vaccine detox, I
haven't really done any research or done anything specific.   I
don't know.   I
saw on the news that Denmark is
imposing a livestock abandonment tax.  It
seems like there's a global trend toward regulation. What do you think?
But I don't really understand this.  I think that because they're trying to regulate this, the
backlash is so strong that it's
kind of been kind of swept under the rug these days
. This
issue has been around for quite some time now.  Well, it's been a while, but
I think the
peculiar thing about those Europeans is that
they've
done everything they can to destroy the environment, and now they
tell people who are trying to destroy the environment that they absolutely
can't do it, but at the same time, they
don't stop the environmental destruction that I've been doing all this time, so it's
incredibly
hypocritical.
Well, in fact, which country isn't like that
? But now, especially in the past when they were
wealthy,
there was a novel called Empire Hunters that I really enjoyed reading, and in
that novel, they just refer to them as robber nations
.  Those old
empires.  Imperialist countries.
So, even in the case of France,
if you look at Europe itself, it's a bit like that.
Now, when importing agricultural products from third world countries, they
ask for a certificate proving that they were produced in an environmentally friendly manner.
But
usually, when you import something like palm oil from places like Southeast Asia, you
grow it there and
export it, but since the farmers who grow it are
all small-scale farmers like in our country, they
can't do that kind of paperwork.  Then, I
say, do it unconditionally.
But the problem is that they act like thugs, threatening to tell us to
do it unconditionally or we won't live there.
On the other hand, if they
make a similar kind of eco-friendly policy for their farmers in their own country,
the farmers will come out with tractors and
plow the roads.
Then, after watching the protest for a while, I realized that I couldn't
do it.  I'll take care of it.   It's
like this.
So, because they have issues with votes and other things within their own country, they
can't enforce anything, so they
just act like thugs to people from weaker countries. But the
problem is that they can act like thugs because they
have the luxury of doing so.   Since
the country has money, it's natural that it's more expensive.
If you do various paperwork and things that are relatively eco-friendly, the
price will go up, but even if the price goes up, we
think that there is a more important value, and
for that, we're going to
spend a little more money and do something about it.
But this is it, so whether
it's good or not, let's
put that aside.  Setting aside that value judgment, the
country can do it because it has the means,
but these days, free trade is under a lot of threat, and there is
almost
no sense of the world being one, and we
are moving into an era where everyone is trying to survive on their own.
hmm.  hmm.
In this situation, I think it will
be difficult to easily touch on issues related to food.   If
you mess with the farmers,
a lot of them will just go out of business.   If you
close down your business, close down your farm, and stop raising cattle,
then after some time passes and you
reach a point where agricultural exports and imports become difficult, it will
be very difficult to start farming again.
Germany, saying it was eco-friendly, went nuclear-free and
did a lot of weird things, but
regardless of whether it was good or bad, they pushed it forward as a policy, but
after the Russia-Ukrainian War broke out, they
were hit hard.
So, if we check this like this
and do something like that, the world trend itself will inevitably
go in that direction, so we will have no choice but to be quite conservative when it comes to touching on food. I agree more than anyone else
that we need to go eco-friendly,
but in reality,
there are many things that the government is doing at its level that are quite rough and ignorant.  So,
I have
absolutely no desire to eat things like glyphosate, and I
wish glyphosate would just be completely banned. Even if it weren't like
that, if the country, government, or organization
just unconditionally
said to stop using glyphosate for some reason, the
technology to farm without using glyphosate would spread, and the number of
farmers who become accustomed to it would increase, and
so in a situation where it would be impossible to maintain food production at a similar level to when glyphosate was used in the past, if we
just
banned glyphosate and food production plummeted and
food tribute prices skyrocketed,
then in the end, the
rich wouldn't care.  The
people who decide on that policy and do that
won't be affected at all.  You can just spend a lot of money and
buy rice, soup, and other food
.  But poor
people just get hit hard by that and
starve to death or have a very difficult life, and
this is like a severance pay and I
think the government has a role to play and the government has a very important role to play,
but I
don't know what this is.
There are many cases where it seems like experts don't really make policy decisions, so
bringing in livestock and ruminants and
saying that they pollute the environment does
n't make sense, but
there's no place to collect the tax, so they collect it from the cows.
Anyway, if you
do that, the farmers will
be nervous, so in fact,
in places like France and Belgium, there
were huge protests.  They
bring out the tractor and plow the road
.   I do
n't think I can handle that.
In my opinion.
yes.  Now, it
seems like all that eco-friendliness is going out of style,
so everyone is losing their leisure time.
I think it's something like that, something that can do things like that.
Please recommend some cuts of lamb and beef that are low in protein and high in fat
.  I've been adding lamb ribs to my child's
diet lately.
What would you recommend?
Anything that is low in fat and low in fat is
now called samgyeopsal.  Representative examples
include lamb samgyeopsal and beef samgyeopsal.
Lamb tends to be a bit
fattier.
But yes, samgyeopsal is good, right?  Flap V
Flap is a type of pork belly that has not had its bones removed
.  Both flaps.   It's
also okay to make something like a stew and eat it by removing all the bones.
Well, there is still quite a bit of
fat between the ribs.
Samgyeopsal is a bit more
fatty than that,
I think.   Do they
sell that kind of lamb rump cap in meat boxes these days?
There are also areas that are almost just fat.
So, if you think of beef, it's the shrimp meat part, but if you think of
lamb, it's just fat, so they used
to sell it like that, but I don't know about now.
Shall we go and see?
70CL
Ah, these things are also 70CL, which
means that 30% of them are fat.  So,
if you look at the fat-to-protein ratio in terms of pure fat, then
when you look at it in terms of pure fat to pure protein, fat is 2 and
protein is 1.  These
things can now be considered very high in fat
.  So, the Paleo Medicinal
ratio is just right.  If you
buy only these and eat them, the Palemishina ratio will
be accurate.
yes.  Well,
actually, this is okay too.
If you think that you're just going to eat cannibals without eating anything, then you're going to eat this and
add some organs or something, because
it's mainly protein and
doesn't have much fat.
Yangseol This is really cheap.   It's
a mutton, isn't it?  The mutton
would have a stronger scent, right?  Doesn't this also have quite a bit of fat
?  This is also a tongue-in-cheek product,
but the price is very cheap.
Anyway, I think both trimmings are really good
.
I'm worried because I drew 70 won, but actually,
like I said last time,
what is
it?  I'm a little less worried about portals and I
don't sell Recap these days.
Oh, the price of lamb has
gone up quite a bit.
In the past, lamb was really cheap, but
now, I used to buy boneless lamb
for about 1,000 won last year
.  I
ate this almost all year last year.  At that time,
the price was around 1,000 won, but now it's
16,200 won, a 60%
increase. Does that make sense?
yes.  Anyway,
would raw fish be good?  The soup is good.   I
heard that sunburn can cause skin discoloration and wrinkles. Am I
doing something wrong?
[Music] If
you receive a sub-circuit,
aging will definitely occur, and this
is nonsense.  Rather, it is true that exposing the skin to
too much sunlight is
definitely not good.  So,
it's not good to receive this much.
It's not good to just receive too much.
There is a level to which the body can recover, and if it
starts to exceed a certain level, then of course it
can get worse. If you actually
take it to that level, your skin will start to
break out, and this causes a
lot of DNA damage, which is really bad
.  But that's not it.
Getting the right amount of sunlight is
actually much better for your skin health.
It's a matter of capacity, but it's much better for your
health to receive it little by little rather than not at all
.  Maybe if
you take too much, it might not be good, and
at the same time, if you take almost none at all and then
just pick one day and
go and take two hours straight, it
can be seriously bad for you.
If you receive it steadily and gradually, your skin will adapt and
it will be better to receive it than not to receive it at all.   I
heard that we and those dogs have a lot of microplastics.  Is it not so good to eat alone
?
Or maybe it's not that many
.  What I mean by a lot is, there
's a lot of water in water bottles, and
there's a lot of water or liquids in plastic-coated containers
.  well.   At
least for now, I think it's better to eat seafood, wild
seafood, and other healthy
seafood that has a lot of nutrients in it than not to eat them
.
It's not like you can completely avoid mass-plasty just by eating meat.
And as I said, I
edited and uploaded the stellate video,
so if we don't eat something, we have
to eat something else.   Because
I just can't live without eating.
In the comments on that video, there were people asking if photosynthesis was the answer,
but
if we could really live by photosynthesis, we
could just photosynthesize without eating clams, but if we
don't eat clams, we'd have to eat something, and
there's no such thing as completely clean food.  Even if we
just eat meat, which is a phthalate bomb among the things we can eat,
I think we need to carefully consider the opportunity cost or what we gain and what we lose when we choose something else.
Hello sir.   The
ocean is polluted by microplastics, heavy metals, and
radiation.
What are your thoughts on this?
As I said before, the
trate of meat will be much higher
.   These
are meats that are now vacuum-packed.   Since
heavy metals
are continuously being tested, you
can just eat seafood with low heavy metal content.  So,
I think eating a lot of things like that might not be good for you.
Things like that, tuna, and things like that.  There is
no need to worry about small fish, so you
can eat them as much as you want, and they are continuously tested for radioactivity,
so as of now, there is not a single seafood product distributed in our country that
requires any concern about radioactivity levels
.
So, when it gets to the point where you need to worry,
then you should stop eating it.   I
found the land.  The land has
n't been stamped or anything like that yet.  Still,
I think we can say that we've almost got it.
I think I'll be going to Gosung, Gangwon-do.
yes.
There are many things I need to prepare for and I'm a bit nervous, but
I'm also a bit lost as to where to start.
First, I
need to build a greenhouse to put my stuff in.
Next year, I'll probably do some pre-sales or
some kind of crowdfunding. I don't think it'll be
until next year, but
I think it'll be done before the end of the year.
Yes, because this year's crop failed here and we don't have the capital to start anew next year.
Oh, I guess I'll have to think about that carefully.
There is nowhere to get pasture-raised sheep or cattle.  There is a pig,
what do you think about that?  Well, it's not bad.   I was
on a one-bite diet when I got pregnant, but I'm having
morning sickness and
can't eat anything but spicy food.
I can't eat meat butter at all.  What
should I do?
hmm.
Rest and eat spicy food.   I
don't know about spicy food, but is there any way to eat meat
with fruit and sour cream
?
Could it be that morning sickness is caused by a lack of cholesterol?  That's what they
say sometimes.
In that case, since a lot of cholesterol is used during pregnancy, and
cholesterol is also a raw material for making bile when eating fat, the
body rejects fatty foods in order to preserve cholesterol.
This theory suggests a hypothesis.   This
is Sellon's theory.  Well, it's not like it's an established theory
.  Anyway,
if you think about it that way, it might be helpful to supplement your diet with foods that are high in cholesterol
.  Of course butter
would be good, but if you can't eat anything else,
how about eggs?   Would
n't it be good to eat a lot of eggs?
If I eat something new like fish carpaccio or sashimi, would I be able to eat it?
I think it would be a good idea to try to utilize that a bit better.
Well,
since the category of carnivore is so broad, even
if it's animal food, whether it's cheese, eggs, or
seafood, I think it would be good to keep a variety of foods
on your radar and eat them
with appropriate seasoning, as
that's much better than not
eating them at all.  no see.
I don't think it's a good idea to just eat whatever you want
.
So, if you
say you ate fried food because you were craving it, it
might actually be better not to eat it.  Now,
try it in a sour meat stew with tomato sauce or a spicy dish with scallion pancakes.
Is Chujangyeon a Gochijang brand?  Jukjang is
that gochujang brand.   This
is a gochujang that does not use soybeans, so it does not contain soybeans.
I have it too.   This is
gochujang made with barley instead of soybeans, so you
can avoid eating soybeans.   I
can't even eat eggs, so I'll try to eat as many as I can
.  These days, I only
eat things like water, seviche, and wheat noodles
.  Oh,
if you can eat ceviche and water, you can make a lot of that
yourself and it's really good
.  That
sounds like a good idea.
Raw milk seems like a good option in those times, but
it's not easy to find.
I envy the sheep that Soyi raised herself.
I would like to sell it.   I
can't eat beef either.  If you
raise a cow like this,
when it turns right, it will just be sent to the slaughterhouse
.  It's so hard to do the above, so we
bring the meat ourselves and
sell it.
Hello, Mr. Couple Scam.  I
came in quickly after seeing the title and listened to the first part from the seating area
.  Is the land issue finally being resolved
?
There was a nobleman in the castle.  It's 40,000 meters long, so it
looks wide enough and the slope is good.
Congratulations, indeed.
Oh no.  It's
not 40,000 M.  I think you
saw it in the picture I showed you earlier, but
that's the land underneath, and in fact, we
may be able to rent that too, but
not yet.
I think it's probably around 20,000 square meters
now.
Actually, if that were the grassland, I would have
just asked you to lend it to me, including the square footage, but
then I said, "Oh,
but that's actually
a bit burdensome."
I think the rent will go up a lot more than it is now.  Oh,
isn't that right?  Well, it might not be like that
.  Although the land here is wide, the
number of animals that can be raised is not that many, and
considering the actual usable area, it doesn't seem like it would be particularly more expensive
.
yes.  Well, anyway, if you try to rent that large piece of land, you can
pay the rent and make a lot of money there for a year,
so there
won't be any problems after that, but anyway, that's
how it is.  yes.  So,
the landowner suddenly asked if he could afford to rent a large lot,
so I
think he will probably only do it for around 20,000M for now.
Well, if we really want to be specific, the land
size may be a bit smaller than it is now.   The
actual usable area is based on land size,
but I don't think it will get any smaller
.
yes.  If I do well next year, I'll probably ask them to
let me borrow the 40,000 M below that
.  Actually, someone else
came there before me and said they
wanted to rent it, and the landowner
said they understood.  I'm
not sure what will happen with that.
I think we'll have to wait and see about that.
Hello G.
Hello, Kim Mi.
Aren't you going to share the restaurant?  Actually, I
don't eat the same thing every day, but
there have been some changes recently.
I
bought a lot of that ham in bulk and have been
eating a lot of ham these days.
And
likewise, I
also bought a lot of that Harino Romano shredded cheese
.  The price for a guesthouse is
8,000 won or something like that, so
the price is ridiculous.
Hoekrenurmano is literally
made from extremely concentrated sheep's milk,
so when 100g is scooped out,
the fat, fat, and protein
are in the mid to high 30g range.  It's an
incredibly concentrated
food with 37g of fat, 34g of protein, and something like that, but it's just ridiculous that it costs 8,000 won
.  So I bought a lot of them
.  yes.  So now
that I have those guys, I cook the
minced meat I bought and
add rice to it
.  I put that in a bowl,
sprinkled cheese on top, mixed it with residual heat to
melt it, and ate it. I
was eating it like this quite often.
Do you think Kegel exercises are effective?  I'm not sure about that.   Because
I didn't look for it or do anything.
yes.  But isn't that also muscle
training anyway?  Any strength training
will be effective if you do it consistently.
Hello Cherry and Little Boy.
Nice to meet you, Autumn Sky.  Drinking water.   I heard that
people are being
careful with bottled water because of microplastics, but what is the
best way to get delicious water?  Oh, there are so many different opinions on water purifiers, so
it's hard to make a decision.
Well, no matter how you change it, it's
much better than drinking bottled water
.  There is too much miss plastic and
too much nano plastic.  I'm
eating this. This
Brita Jeongsuk.  These days,
there are domestic products that come out with a similar feel, and they say that they are at least better in performance and cleaner and things like that.   I
think it would be good to look for things like that and compare them before purchasing. This
is also made of plastic, but
there are actually some that come out as glass on the outside
. The inside
is also plastic.  Inside Brita.   I'm
not sure if there's anything that's entirely glass
.  I don't know if it's been released yet or
if it's difficult to make, but I don't think
it's
available yet.
I don't think there are many.  But anyway,
even though this is plastic,
most of the miss-plastic is generated during the injection process, so if you just wash it once, there will be
much less of a miss-plastic problem inside the water bottle.  But since I
don't expose it to sunlight all the time and
I've
already rinsed it once
before using it, it
's much better.
And the most certain thing is to
install a Yeoksam water purifier.
Because now it's literally like removing everything from the water,
leaving almost nothing but water
.
yes.  After doing that, it
would be good to add minerals and eat it.
I also do that and
always drink things like Mega Mag for a long time.
Could you elaborate further on the issue of phosphate contamination when shrink-coating meat?  Oh, I
'd like to know in detail which songs I'm listening to are highly polluted.  But isn't this
a bit ambiguous to explain in detail
?  So, I
think that this is probably the first time that we have done this with so many different samples from so many different angles
.
yes.  yes.  First of all,
when an animal is slaughtered, an
acidic solution is sprayed on the outside to prevent bacteria from multiplying,
and then when the acidic meat that has been sprayed
like that
is put into a heat shrink film, these acids melt the polyethylene inside the heat shrink film and
release phthalates.  It's something like this.  So I
think this is the basic concept now.
Well,
to reduce the level of pollution here,
as I mentioned before, it would be relatively better to either go with
bulk imports, or to import meat that has been minced or already minced
.  But since
the meats mixed inside are all cooked together, rather than just sprinkled on the outside, wouldn't
that cook the meats at once and
reduce the exposure to phthalates?  After all, they say that the mountain is melting
.  I think so
.   I
understand that Gosung is a city with a population decline and that it benefits from being empty.
Look carefully and you'll probably find a young farmer in that area
holding on tight.
uh.
But there was something strange about this,
so I looked into it.   When I went
into the agricultural and fishery center at Goseong County Office and looked into the support programs for returning farmers and villagers and
other benefits, I saw that there were a lot of
candidate sites that I had been considering going to in other local governments,
so I
saw a lot of different flowers. I think there were at least five or six of them wherever I looked.
The agricultural village support project
itself.  What is it?
What is it? For example, Pyeongtaek
or something like that.  A place very close to the metropolitan area
.
But, the Gosung
County Office is the only
government-run project that all local governments do, and
that is the support project for purchasing houses in rural areas.
It is a project that lends 300 million won to purchase land.
There was nothing else.  So
I don't know.  I was thinking of calling and asking if there was anything else,
but there were far fewer support programs than I thought. They only
had the basic baseline that all local governments have, and
nothing else.   I
was thinking of doing something like this here.
Of course, I didn't receive anything from Gimcheon either
.
yes.
We've been looking for land to start a family farm for
exactly two years now, and I
finally understand what they mean when they say it takes at least three years for people to look for land
.  I think I'm
starting to get a little more grounded because I keep earning money
.  The Goseong land you recently acquired
looks excellent in terms of slope, accessibility, and usability.  I was informed that the scope of assistance available to me would expand once I was confirmed as a resident of Gwangmok Ecological Livestock Farm
.
Even if you are in a rental state, if you write a good business plan, you
can receive support for pasture-raised livestock farming
.  They
say the next business-related announcement will be made around November or December, so it
would be a good idea to call them around then.
yes.  I was also thinking about certifying pasture-based ecological livestock farming
.  yes.  But
now, I'm a
little bit hesitant about receiving something like that. The reason I
didn't receive support for returning to farming villages or for young entrepreneurs is because if I did
receive something like that, I would be tied to it a little bit.
In fact, we haven't even finished talking about how many years the
contract will be for here yet
.
With that landowner.  In cases like this,
in my Gimcheon, it's a 3-year contract,
so if you're a young farmer,
or if the country
designates you as a successor farmer and
gives you a lease or loan, you have to
stay in that area for at least 15 years
.  Or,
after all the loans have been repaid,
there are things like whether there will be disadvantages in receiving support in the future or whether it will not be possible at all, etc.
So, there were some ambiguous parts about running around like a grasshopper here and there on a rental basis,
but of course, if possible, I would
like to change it.  But on the
other hand, there is also this.   I do
n't know for sure what Yangmok Ecological Livestock Farm supports because I haven't looked into 2024 or 2025, but when I was looking into that kind of stuff in the past,
I saw a lot of it.
Until then, what
they supported was
loans for the cost of building fences and the cost
of purchasing seeds needed to develop the land,
but in
reality, the costs they heard were
n't that high, so it
was just like that.
So, the amount of money for renting out
the alternative living resource development cost for converting forests into grassland is
huge,
so if this person can receive that,
that would be great, but where I am right now, it
is a field anyway, so it is
still designated as land, but it
is about to be changed to a field soon.  It
would have been really nice if it had been changed from pasture to pasture, but unfortunately that's
not the case.
Yes, I
think I'll have to look into it again.  Yeah,
yeah.
Oh, and actually, I
'm in Gosung, and I'm not the only one going in.
Actually, you and I
have talked about this a few times.  Once or
twice.   Would
n't it be possible for other people, besides me, to come in like this towards Goseong and go to a place that feels a bit like a traditional village?  Especially
once I'm settled in.  That's what
I expect.  Because
I do
n't really know how much I can say about this person, but
anyway, this person is
doing a lot of amazing things like this.
So
you keep making grasslands with it.  This
seems like a very special case, and I do
n't think there are many people in our country who do this,
but anyway, it's almost like a paper manufacturing machine
.
So I think he has a
lot of relatively small pastures
.  About 5,000 square meters.
So, in addition to the land I was going to
show you in pictures earlier, you
showed me two other places that I had decided to go to, and it
seems like there are many other lands, and
many of them are actually pastures and ranch lands according to the Pasture Land Act
.  But they are all
flat lands without any slopes or anything like that,
and the size is about 5,000 pyeong
.  But
I think 5.5 rating could be good enough depending on how you do it.  Especially in the case of grassland, there are
now
fewer restrictions on the number of animals raised, so there is
no need to build processing facilities.
So yes.
Wouldn't it be nice if not only me, but other people came and did it together?  So he says he will
continue to create grasslands in the future
.
So, as the pastures continue to expand, I
think that, of course,
only farmers are here, and
I don't think that's the case at all. If
there's a farm like this, I
think there are a lot of business models that can be built around that farm.
Just like that Joslatin always says.
Like that.  But anyway, especially
in the early stages, it might be a little easier if
people who farm in a similar way to me come in,
but
yeah.  Anyway, the
grasslands are not that far apart from each other, and they are quite densely packed, so they
are about 5,000 pyeong in size.
So, later on,
since you said that you would continue to make more grasslands,
one or two more people came and
I was able to stabilize what I was doing to a certain extent and said, "
Oh, that's all I have to do
."  I thought that since that guy had been working hard and trying to do it,
it now seemed like it was a bit useful, and that
it would be good if other people came and did it together once they got the hang of it
.
I have an acquaintance who
went to Goseong and got a scholarship, and I heard that he gets support while on the boat. I'll
ask him about it and
tell you more about it on Abang next week.
Ah, I think Gui-eo will be learning
Mandarin at a place other than the Agricultural Technology Center, but I wonder if there will be
something different in Gui-eo Village
.
yes.  There wasn't as much support for returning to farming as I thought
.  I don't know.
Besides, I guess I'll have to call and ask if there's anything they're doing separately that's not written down anymore
.
But now it's past 11:30, so
we'll be wrapping up the broadcast.  I'll try to turn it on again next week
.  I'll wake up early tomorrow and
go milk the cows, who aren't producing much milk
.  Thank you for watching today
.
Next week,
next week on the 29th.  It's really a goal, and
time flies so quickly.
Now, we're
building a greenhouse in Gosung, preparing to move, and dealing with
all the complicated issues, but
somehow things will work out.  yes.  Anyway,
thank you for watching.
If there are any more things, I
'll share them with you next week.
yes.